{"items": [{"question": "specialist of the gums and other structures around the teeth", "answer": "Periodontist", "options": ["endodontist", "barometer", "optometrist", "Periodontist"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A dentist specializing in diseases of the dental pulp and nerve", "answer": "endodontist", "options": ["sphygmomanometer", "optometrist", "endodontist", "barometer"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A person skilled in testing for defects of vision in order to prescribe corrective glasses", "answer": "optometrist", "options": ["barometer", "optometrist", "sphygmomanometer", "osteopathy"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "any instrument that measures atmospheric pressure.", "answer": "barometer", "options": ["chiropractor", "sphygmomanometer", "barometer", "osteopathy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Measuring Blood pressure", "answer": "sphygmomanometer", "options": ["chiromancy", "chiropractor", "osteopathy", "sphygmomanometer"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Therapy based on the assumption that restoring health is best accomplished by manipulating the skeleton and muscles", "answer": "osteopathy", "options": ["osteopathy", "chiropractor", "octopus", "chiromancy"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "one who manipulates body structures (especially the spine) with hands to relieve low back pain or even headache or high blood pressure", "answer": "chiropractor", "options": ["platypus", "octopus", "chiropractor", "chiromancy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "palmistry.", "answer": "chiromancy", "options": ["chiromancy", "podium", "octopus", "platypus"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "any octopod of the genus having a soft", "answer": "octopus", "options": ["octopus", "platypus", "tripod", "podium"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Small densely furred aquatic monotreme of Australia and Tasmania having a broad bill and tail and webbed feet only species in the family Ornithorhynchidae", "answer": "platypus", "options": ["tripod", "platypus", "podiatrist", "podium"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "a small platform for the conductor of an orchestra", "answer": "podium", "options": ["podium", "tripod", "podiatrist", "graphology"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a stool", "answer": "tripod", "options": ["podiatrist", "graphology", "tripod", "chirographer"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "a person qualified to diagnose and treat foot disorders.", "answer": "podiatrist", "options": ["chirographer", "graphology", "podiatrist", "calligraphy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "the study of handwriting", "answer": "graphology", "options": ["chirographer", "graphology", "calligraphy", "cacography"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "person who does beautiful handwriting penmanship.", "answer": "chirographer", "options": ["calligraphy", "cardiography", "chirographer", "cacography"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "highly decorative handwriting", "answer": "calligraphy", "options": ["calligraphy", "cardiography", "cacography", "photography"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "bad handwriting poor penmanship.", "answer": "cacography", "options": ["telegraphy", "cardiography", "cacography", "photography"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "recording the activity of the heart electronically", "answer": "cardiography", "options": ["photography", "biography", "cardiography", "telegraphy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "the process or art of producing images of objects.", "answer": "photography", "options": ["telegraphy", "biography", "geriatrician", "photography"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Communicating at a distance by electric transmission over wire", "answer": "telegraphy", "options": ["telegraphy", "biography", "geriatrician", "senescent"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "a written account of another person's life", "answer": "biography", "options": ["biography", "geriatrician", "senior", "senescent"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "specialist in the branch of medicine dealing with the diseases and problems specific to old people", "answer": "geriatrician", "options": ["geriatrician", "senior", "senescent", "senate"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "growing old aging.", "answer": "senescent", "options": ["Periodontist", "senate", "senescent", "senior"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "older or elder", "answer": "senior", "options": ["endodontist", "senate", "senior", "Periodontist"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "an assembly or council of citizens having the highest deliberative functions in a government", "answer": "senate", "options": ["optometrist", "endodontist", "Periodontist", "senate"], "answer_index": 4}], "title": "Session 9 to 10.txt", "total": 25}